A Guide to the International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records FA1838
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Files, 1991-2021; 1; 14.9 Cubic Feet 38 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
  - Africa Regional Meetings, Stellenbosch, 2011 (Box 103, Folder 1180)
  - 5th ISTR Asia Pacific Regional Conference, Philippines, 2007 (Box 103, Folder 1181)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Quito, 2017 (Box 103, Folder 1182)
  - Asia Pacific Conference, Jakarta, 2017 (Box 104, Folder 1183)
  - Asia Pacific Conference, Jakarta - PhD Students, 2017 (Box 104, Folder 1184)
  - Regional Networks Taskforce, 2011 (Box 104, Folder 1185)
  - Asia Pacific Korea Aid, 2011-2014 (Box 104, Folder 1186)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Chile, 2011-2013 (Box 104, Folder 1187)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Puerto Rico, 2014-2015 (Box 104, Folder 1188)
  - 2019 Africa PhD Seminar, Johannesburg, 2018-2019 (Box 104, Folder 1189)
  - Africa Regional Network, 2016-2018 (Box 104, Folder 1190)
  - Africa - Accra, 2013-2017 (Box 104, Folder 1191)
  - Africa Conference/Board, 2017 (Box 104, Folder 1192)
  - 4th Africa Regional Conference - Civil Society and Philanthropy in Africa: Contradictions, Possibilities, 2017 (Box 105, Folder 1193)
  - 4th Africa Regional Conference - Program, 2017 (Box 105, Folder 1194)
  - 4th Africa Regional Conference - West Africa Civil Society Institute (WACSI), 2016-2017 (Box 105, Folder 1195)
  - West Africa Civil Society Institute (WACSI) - Memorandum of Agreement, 2016 (Box 105, Folder 1196)
  - 3rd Africa Regional Conference, Accra, 2016 (Box 105, Folder 1197-1198)
  - Africa Regional Network - Southern Africa Trust Host, 2011-2014 (Box 105, Folder 1199)
  - Africa Regional Network, 2014-2015 (Box 105, Folder 1200)
  - Rene Bekker - Global Philanthropic Studies Erasmus Mundus Joint Doctorate, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 1201)
  - Japan National Tourist Organization, 1997 (Box 105, Folder 1202)
  - Ford Foundation, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 1203)
  - Ford Foundation - Vietnam/China, 2006 (Box 105, Folder 1204)
  - Ford Foundation - Brazil, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1205)
  - Ford Foundation - India, 2000 (Box 105, Folder 1206)
  - Ford Foundation - Cairo, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 1207)
  - Ford Foundation - Mexico, 1995 (Box 105, Folder 1208)
  - Gilman Foundation and Others, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1209)
  - Fondazione San Paolo Di Torino, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1210)
  - The Bank of Sweden Tercentenary Foundation, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1211)
  - Arab Gulf Programme for UN Development Organizations, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1212)
  - Lilly Endowment, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1213)
  - Kuwait Awqaf Public Foundation, 1998 (Box 106, Folder 1214)
  - Fondazione Giovanni Agnelli, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 1215)
  - Getting to the Sources of Philanthropy in the Americas, Rockefeller Archive Center, 2010 (Box 106, Folder 1216)
  - Global Philanthropy, Rockefeller Archive Center, 2007-2010 (Box 106, Folder 1217)
  - PhD Seminar Proposal, 2015 (Box 106, Folder 1218)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Conference, Buenos Aires, 2011 (Box 106, Folder 1219)
  - Regional Conference, Mexico City, 2009 (Box 106, Folder 1220)
  - Institute of International Education - Mexico, 2013 (Box 106, Folder 1221)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Regional Meeting, Mexico City, 2009 (Box 106, Folder 1222)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network - Coordination, 2004-2012 (Box 106, Folder 1223)
  - Asia Pacific Regional Meeting, China, 2013 (Box 106, Folder 1224)
  - Tsinghua International Conference on Philanthropy, 2015 (Box 106, Folder 1225)
  - Institutional Philanthropy Project, 2016 (Box 106, Folder 1226)
  - Mentoring Program, 2016-2017 (Box 107, Folder 1227)
  - Mentoring Program - Mentors, 2016 (Box 107, Folder 1228)
  - Mentoring Program - Mentees, 2016 (Box 107, Folder 1229)
  - Mentoring Program, 2016-2018 (Box 107, Folder 1230)
  - PhD Alumni Meeting, 2016-2017 (Box 107, Folder 1231)
  - International Research Fund, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 1232)
  - Nonprofit Research Grants, 2000 (Box 107, Folder 1233)
  - Ford Foundation - Grant 1, 1992-1995 (Box 107, Folder 1234)
  - Ford Foundation - Grant, 2000-2001 (Box 107, Folder 1235)
  - Ford Foundation - Proposals, 2001-2005 (Box 107, Folder 1236)
  - Ford Foundation - Proposals, 2004-2007 (Box 107, Folder 1237)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropies - Proposal, 2001-2005 (Box 107, Folder 1238)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropic Service Company - Grant Forms, 1999-2002 (Box 107, Folder 1239)
  - TARA Consultants, 1997-1998 (Box 107, Folder 1240)
  - International Fund Proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 108, Folder 1241)
  - Bellagio, 2000 (Box 108, Folder 1242)
  - Third Sector Response - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Network, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 1243)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropies - Proposal, 1993-2001 (Box 108, Folder 1244)
  - International Third-Sector Research Fund - Proposal, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 1245)
  - International Civil Society Fund Meeting, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 1246)
  - Olga Toro - Fund Consultant, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 1247)
  - Ford Foundation - World Civil Society Project, 1999 (Box 108, Folder 1248)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropic - ISTR Progress Report, 1992-1994; 1992 September-1993 December (Box 108, Folder 1249)
  - The Atlantic Philanthropic - ISTR Progress Report, 1994-1995 (Box 108, Folder 1250)
  - Fondation de France, 1993-1997 (Box 109, Folder 1251)
  - David and Lucile Packard Foundation, 1998-2003 (Box 109, Folder 1252)
  - Voluntas Symposium - The Nonprofit Sector at the Cross-Road? An International Policy Symposium, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 1253-1254)
  - ISTR's 10th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 109, Folder 1255)
  - ISTR's 10th Anniversary, undated (Box 109, Folder 1255)
- Board of Directors, 1992-2021; 2; 9.97 Cubic Feet 25 letter document boxes, 1 legal document box
  - General, 1992-2016; 2.1
    - ISTR Board of Directors, 1992-1998 (Box 112, Folder 1297)
    - Strategic Plan, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 615)
    - Nonprofit Academic Centers Council Members List, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 616)
    - Projects, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 617)
    - Publications, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 618)
    - Strategic Directions 2005-2009, 2005-2006 (Box 61, Folder 621)
    - Reflections on ISTR's Future Strategy, Alan Fowler, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 622)
    - Strategy Forms, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 623)
    - ISTR's Strategy 2005-2009: A Position Paper for Discussion and Comment, Draft 1, 1999-2005 (Box 61, Folder 624)
    - Evaluation and Long Term Plan, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 625)
    - Strategic and Long-Range Planning Consultant Interview Process, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 626)
    - ISTR Evaluation and Strategic Planning Presentation, Sylvie Tsyboula and Russy D. Sumariwalla, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 627)
    - Strategic Plan, 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 628)
    - Strategic Plan, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 629)
    - Strategic Plan - Further Flowering of ISTR 2000-2005, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 632)
    - Strategic Planning, 2003-2004 (Box 62, Folder 633)
    - Memos, 2003-2006 (Box 62, Folder 634)
    - Issues, 2002-2003 (Box 62, Folder 635)
    - Standing Committee on Research and Publications: Terms of Reference Handbook, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 636)
    - "MBD" Materials, 2000-2002 (Box 62, Folder 638)
    - Board Schedule, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 664)
    - Strategic Directions, 2005 (Box 64, Folder 665)
    - Board Handbook, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 732)
    - Memos, 2013 (Box 68, Folder 733)
    - Strategic Directions Background Material, 2016 (Box 72, Folder 770)
    - Strategic Plan: 2016-2021, 2015-2016 (Box 72, Folder 771)
    - ISTR's Executive Officer: A Position Review and Analysis with Recommendations, Leonard Stern, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 872)
    - Board Handbook, 2004 (Box 112, Folder 1291)
      Also includes "Hosting ISTR-Related Conferences: Memorandum of Understanding for Collaboration in Global Conferences."
    - Board Handbook, undated (Box 112, Folder 1292)
      Also contains "The ISTR Standing Committee on Fundraising Committee: Terms of Reference."
  - Executive Committee, 1994-2021; 2.2
    Subseries 2.2 primarily contains minutes, agendas, and correspondence relating to the meetings of the Executive Committee.
    Arrangement
    This subseries is arranged chronologically.
    - 1994 Meeting Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 524)
    - 1995 Meeting Materials, Conference Call (Box 52, Folder 525)
    - 1998 Meeting Materials, University of Geneva, 1995-1998 (Box 52, Folder 526)
    - 1998 Meeting Materials, Brighton, England, 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 607)
    - 1999 Meeting Materials, Pocantico, New York (Box 84, Folder 905)
    - 2002 Meeting Materials, Paris, France (Box 53, Folder 527)
    - 2003 Meeting Materials, Bologna, Italy, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 528)
    - Memorandum of Understanding for Collaboration in Regional Conferences, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 529)
    - 2004 Meeting Materials, Paris, France (Box 62, Folder 637)
    - 2006 Meeting Materials, Tarrytown, New York, 2005-2006 (Box 53, Folder 530)
    - 2008 Meeting Materials, Conference Call, 2007-2008 (Box 60, Folder 619)
    - 2011 Meeting Materials, Conference Call (Box 60, Folder 609)
    - 2012 Meeting Materials (Box 62, Folder 639)
    - 2013 Meeting Materials (Box 69, Folder 736)
    - 2013 Meeting Materials, University of Muenster, Germany (Box 69, Folder 737)
    - 2014 Meeting Materials, Skype (Box 53, Folder 531)
    - 2015 Meeting Materials, Frankfurt, Germany, 2015-2016 (Box 53, Folder 532)
    - 2016 Meeting Materials, Skype, 2015-2016 (Box 53, Folder 533)
    - 2017 Meeting Materials, Ghent, Belgium (Box 53, Folder 534)
    - 2018 Meeting Materials, Dublin, Ireland, 2017-2018 (Box 53, Folder 535)
    - 2019 Meeting Materials, Bangkok, Thailand (Box 53, Folder 536)
    - 2019 Meeting Materials, Zoom (Box 53, Folder 537)
    - 2020 Meeting Materials, Zoom (Box 54, Folder 538)
      Closed - Open in 2025
    - 2021 Meeting Materials, Zoom (Box 54, Folder 539)
  - Elections, 1994-2018; 2.3
    Subseries 2.3 contains nominating committee materials, nominee biographies, ballots, and general correspondence relating to elections held for the Board of Directors.
    - Nominations, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 424)
    - Board Elections, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 425)
    - Nominating and Elections Procedures, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 438)
    - Ballots, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 772-773)
    - Nominating Committee, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 774)
    - Nominating Committee, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 775)
    - Election, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 776)
    - Biographical Information, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 777)
    - Biographical Information, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 777)
    - Nominating Committee Correspondence, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 193)
    - Nominating Committee, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - Nominating Ballot, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - Nominating Bio Information, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - Nominating Committee 2002, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 426)
    - Nominees Information 2002 (Box 42, Folder 427)
    - Nominating Committee Issues, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 201)
    - Nominating and Ballot Issues, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - Nominating Committee, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 198)
    - Nominees Rejected, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 199)
    - Nominating Committee Report, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 200)
    - Nominating Bios, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 202)
    - Board Elections, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 203)
    - Nominating Committee, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 204)
    - Nominees, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 205)
    - Nominating Committee, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 778)
    - Nominating Committee - Benjamin Gidron (Chair), 2008-2009 (Box 73, Folder 779)
    - Election, 2008 (Box 73, Folder 780)
    - Nominating Committee, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 781-782)
    - Election, 2010 (Box 74, Folder 783)
    - Nominating Committee, 2012 (Box 74, Folder 784-785)
    - Nominating Committee, 2014 (Box 74, Folder 786)
    - Nominating Committee, 2016 (Box 74, Folder 787)
    - Nominating Committee, 2018 (Box 74, Folder 788)
  - Board Meetings, 1992-2021; 2.4
    Subseries 2.4 contains meeting minutes, agendas, and general correspondence related to various board meetings.
    - Budapest, Hungary, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 870)
    - Minutes - ISTR Board Meetings, 1992-2017 (Box 112, Folder 1296)
      Comprehensive collection of minutes from the years 1992-2017.
    - Retreat at Leeds Castle, Maidstone, England, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 431-433)
    - Retreat and Election at Leeds Castle, Maidstone, England, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 871)
    - Pécs/Budapest, Hungary, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 434)
    - Baltimore, Maryland, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 437)
    - Mexico City, Mexico, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 439)
    - Barcelona, Spain, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 883)
    - Barcelona, Spain, 1997 (Box 83, Folder 901)
    - Geneva, Switzerland, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 430)
    - Retreat at the Pocantico Conference Center of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Tarrytown, New York, 1998-1999 (Box 84, Folder 902-904)
    - Alexandria, Virginia, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 429)
    - Alexandria, Virginia, 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 435-436)
    - Alexandria, Virginia - Evaluation/Minutes, 1999 (Box 44, Folder 435)
    - Santiago, Chile, 1999 (Box 112, Folder 1290)
    - Santiago, Chile - 3/4 (Box 112, Folder 1290)
    - Santiago, Chile - 4/4 (Box 112, Folder 1290)
    - Dublin, Ireland, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 428)
    - Madrid, Spain, 2001 (Box 51, Folder 512-513)
    - Cape Town, South Africa, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 500)
    - Cape Town, South Africa - ISTR Board Minutes 02, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 500)
    - Bologna, Italy, 2003 (Box 62, Folder 630-631)
    - Toronto, Canada, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 501-502)
    - Oslo, Norway, 2005 (Box 50, Folder 504-506)
    - Oslo, Norway - International Research Conference on Religious Non-Government Organizations (NGOs), 2005 (Box 50, Folder 507)
    - Bangkok, Thailand, 2006 (Box 50, Folder 508-509)
    - Brussels, Belgium, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 510-511)
    - Barcelona, Spain, 2008 (Box 61, Folder 620)
    - Mexico City, Mexico, 2009 (Box 60, Folder 611)
    - Istanbul, Turkey, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 612)
    - Pocantico, New York, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 614)
    - Siena, Italy, 2011 (Box 60, Folder 608)
    - Siena, Italy, 2011 (Box 62, Folder 640-641)
    - Seoul, South Korea, 2013 (Box 51, Folder 515)
    - Seoul, South Korea, 2013 (Box 68, Folder 734-735)
    - Muenster, Germany, 2014 (Box 51, Folder 514)
    - San Juan, Puerto Rico, 2015 (Box 51, Folder 516-517)
    - Stokholm, Sweden, 2016 (Box 51, Folder 518-519)
    - Accra, Ghana, 2017 (Box 52, Folder 520)
    - Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 2018 (Box 52, Folder 521)
    - Amsterdam, The Netherlands, 2018 (Box 112, Folder 1293)
    - Bangkok, Thailand, 2019 (Box 112, Folder 1294)
    - Teleconference, Zoom, 2019 (Box 52, Folder 522-523)
    - Teleconference, Zoom, 2020; 2021 (Box 111, Folder 1287)
- Membership, 1992-2020; 3; 4.56 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes
  Series 3 contains membership directories, surveys, statistics, and meeting minutes.
  - Membership Support, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 560)
  - Membership Support, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 561)
  - Membership Questionnaire, 1994 (Box 111, Folder 1282)
  - Membership Directories, 1994-2001 (Box 2, Folder 23-27)
  - Copies of Membership Directories, 1994-2001 (Box 112, Folder 1288-1289)
  - Membership, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 707)
  - Supporting Members, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 703)
  - Supporting Members, 1995-1999 (Box 67, Folder 704)
  - Membership Evaluation Report, Liz Farber, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 653)
  - 1998 Membership Survey, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 655)
  - Membership Survey, 2002 (Box 56, Folder 567)
  - Membership Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 65, Folder 683)
  - Tarr-Whelan Consulting, ISTR Membership Recruitment and Development, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 680)
  - Membership Consultant Research, 2003 (Box 65, Folder 684-685)
  - Membership and Communications Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 65, Folder 679)
  - Membership Report, 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 688)
  - Membership brochures, 2004-2020 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - 2004 Membership Brochure, 2003-2004 (Box 66, Folder 692)
  - 2004 Membership Statistics, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 710)
  - 2005 Membership Statistics, 2004-2005 (Box 67, Folder 711)
  - 2005-2006 Membership, 2004-2006 (Box 67, Folder 712)
  - 2007 Membership, 2004-2007 (Box 67, Folder 714)
  - 2008 Membership, 2006-2008 (Box 67, Folder 715)
  - Membership Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 67, Folder 713)
  - Membership Issue Bangkok, 2006 (Box 67, Folder 716)
  - Foundation Letters, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 705)
  - Institutional Members, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 706)
  - Memos to Members, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 708)
  - Members, 2008 (Box 111, Folder 1283)
  - Membership, 2009 (Box 67, Folder 709)
  - General Membership Meeting, Kadir Has University, 2010 (Box 60, Folder 610)
  - Membership Committee, 2011 (Box 68, Folder 722)
  - 2012 Membership, 2011-2012 (Box 68, Folder 723)
  - Membership Meeting, 2012 (Box 63, Folder 656)
  - Membership Renewal, 2012-2014 (Box 68, Folder 724)
  - 2013 Membership, undated (Box 111, Folder 1284)
  - General Membership Meeting, University of Muenster, 2014 (Box 63, Folder 649)
  - 2014-2015 Membership, undated (Box 68, Folder 725)
  - 2014-2015 Membership, 2013-2015 (Box 111, Folder 1285)
  - Membership Survey, 2015 (Box 68, Folder 726)
  - 2016-2017 Membership (Box 111, Folder 1286)
  - General Membership Meeting, Stockholm, Sweden, 2016 (Box 63, Folder 646)
- Conference Planning Material, 1990-2018; 4; 15.95 Cubic Feet 42 letter document boxes
  Series 4 contains planning material for ISTR's international conferences. It includes information on conference sites, conference programs, schedules, and correspondence with speakers, hosts, advisors, and the conference planning committee.
  This series is arranged chronologically by conference year.
  - General, 1997-2018
    - Conference Statistics and Grading, 2004-2006 (Box 111, Folder 1273)
    - Abstract Reviewer Letters, 2005-2006 (Box 111, Folder 1274)
    - Conference Site Criteria, 1997-2002 (Box 111, Folder 1275)
    - Conference Site Criteria, 2002 (Box 111, Folder 1276)
    - Conference Site Criteria, 2008-2010 (Box 111, Folder 1277)
    - Conference Site Criteria, 2010-2014 (Box 111, Folder 1278)
    - Conference Hosting Inquiries, 2012-2013 (Box 111, Folder 1279)
    - Indianapolis Conference Bids, 2013 (Box 111, Folder 1280)
    - Conference Site Criteria, 2016-2018 (Box 111, Folder 1281)
  - 1st International Conference - Pécs, Hungary, 1990-1995
    - Conference Organizing Committee Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 116)
    - African Scholars, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 117)
    - Amitai Etzioni, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 118)
    - Conference Survey, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 119)
    - Conference Structure, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 120)
    - Publications Display, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 121)
    - Pécs - General, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 122)
    - Pécs - General, 1992-1994 (Box 45, Folder 448)
    - Pécs - General, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 606)
    - Scholarships, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - 1994 Conference Inquiry, 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 443)
    - Conference Brochure/Registration Booklet, 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 445)
    - Call for Papers, 1993-1995 (Box 57, Folder 581)
    - Conference Program, 1994 (Box 57, Folder 582)
    - Abstracts, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 583-584)
    - Abstracts, 1993-1994 (Box 59, Folder 602-604)
    - Session Moderators, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 585)
    - General Meeting, Janus Pannonius University, 1994 (Box 58, Folder 586)
    - Abstracts and Papers Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 59, Folder 601)
    - Conference Details, 1993-1995 (Box 59, Folder 605)
  - 2nd International Conference - Mexico City, Mexico, 1993-2001
    - Scholarships, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 577)
    - Mexico City - General, 1994-1995 (Box 81, Folder 873)
    - Universidad Iberoamericana, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 874)
    - Jose Luis Mendez, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 875)
    - Conference Logistics, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 876)
    - Benjamin Gidron, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 877)
    - Estelle James, Keynote, 1995-1996 (Box 81, Folder 878)
    - Victor Urquidi, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 879)
    - Speakers - Francis Fukuyama, Robert Putnam, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 880)
    - Conference Handouts, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 881)
    - Affinity Group Meetings, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 882)
    - El Colegio de Mexico, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 969)
    - Panel Sessions, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 970)
    - Charities Aid Foundation, 1993-2001 (Box 89, Folder 971)
    - European Network, 1996 (Box 89, Folder 972)
    - Arab NGO Network, 1996 (Box 90, Folder 973)
    - Ireland Third Sector, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 974)
    - Eastern and Central Europe, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 1097)
    - Latin America, undated (Box 97, Folder 1098)
    - Articles, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 1099)
    - Inquiries, 1995-1996 (Box 109, Folder 1256)
    - Conference Feedback, 1996-1997 (Box 109, Folder 1257)
    - ISTR General Meeting, 1995-1996 (Box 109, Folder 1258)
  - 3rd International Conference - Geneva, Switzerland, 1995-2002
    - Working Papers Author Consent Forms, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 228)
    - Working Papers Series, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 229)
    - Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC), 2000 (Box 22, Folder 230)
    - Fundraising, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 446)
    - Bridging the Gap Pre-Conference Workshop, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 447)
    - Methodology Pre-Conference Workshop, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 449)
    - Fundraising, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 450)
    - Gidron, Benjamin, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 451)
    - Confirmed Moderators, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 452)
    - Evaluations, Conference Proceedings, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 471)
    - Conference Brochure, Programming Ideas, 1996-1999 (Box 47, Folder 472)
    - Thank Yous, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 540)
    - Funding Multinational, 1997-2001 (Box 54, Folder 541)
    - Conference Chairs, Themes, 1995-2002 (Box 54, Folder 542)
    - Conference Program, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 553)
    - Workshop Registrations, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 554)
    - Nongovernmental Organizations: The Challenge of Partnership, Mary Robinson, UN Commissioner for Human Rights, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 555)
    - Publications Display, 1996-2000 (Box 55, Folder 556)
    - Call for Proposals, 1996-1998 (Box 55, Folder 557)
    - Geneva - General, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 558)
    - Conference Evaluations, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 578)
    - Tourism, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 579)
    - Presenters, 1998 (Box 57, Folder 580)
    - Abstract Authors, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 587)
    - Panel Proposals, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 588)
    - Arts and Culture Panel, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 589)
    - Paper Sessions, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 590)
    - Poster Sessions, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 591)
    - Abstract Reviewers, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 592)
    - Abstract Grading, Marilyn Taylor, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 593)
    - Unreviewed Abstracts, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 594)
    - Abstracts, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 595)
    - General Membership Meeting, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 596)
    - Press, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 597)
    - Plenary, "The Social Economy: The European Union and the Third Sector: What Does the Future Hold?", 1998 (Box 58, Folder 598)
    - Participant List, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 599)
    - Accepted Abstracts, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 600)
    - Funding Issues, 1997 (Box 110, Folder 1259)
  - 4th International Conference - Dublin, Ireland, 1997-2000
    - Participant List, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 222)
    - Participant List, 2000 (Box 47, Folder 474)
    - Accepted Presenters, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 223)
    - Conference Sessions, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 224)
    - Conference Evaluations, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 225)
    - Follow Up Correspondence, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 226)
    - Bertelsmann Stiftung Conference Publications, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 231)
    - AVINA, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 232)
    - Dublin - General, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 233)